<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <MSE_EndoskeletonStimulator.label>endoskeleton stimulator</MSE_EndoskeletonStimulator.label>
  <MSE_EndoskeletonStimulator.description>A torso implant that stimulates the overall muscles so they can operate at maximum performance. Requires implants research before installing.</MSE_EndoskeletonStimulator.description>

  <MSE_MuscleStimulator.label>muscle stimulator</MSE_MuscleStimulator.label>
  <MSE_MuscleStimulator.description>A muscle implant that stimulates the overall muscles so they can operate at maximum performance. Requires implants research before installing.</MSE_MuscleStimulator.description>

  <MSE_BuilderAI.label>builder AI</MSE_BuilderAI.label>
  <MSE_BuilderAI.description>A brain implant that contain AI. Capable to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for building. Requires brain implants research before installing.</MSE_BuilderAI.description>

  <MSE_FarmerAI.label>farmer AI</MSE_FarmerAI.label>
  <MSE_FarmerAI.description>A brain implant that contain AI. Capable to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for farming. Requires brain implants research before installing.</MSE_FarmerAI.description>

  <MSE_DoctorAI.label>doctor AI</MSE_DoctorAI.label>
  <MSE_DoctorAI.description>A brain implant that contain AI. Capable to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for doctoring. Requires brain implants research before installing.</MSE_DoctorAI.description>

  <MSE_MinerAI.label>miner AI</MSE_MinerAI.label>
  <MSE_MinerAI.description>A brain implant that contain AI. Capable to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for mining. Requires brain implants research before installing.</MSE_MinerAI.description>

  <MSE_DiplomatAI.label>diplomat AI</MSE_DiplomatAI.label>
  <MSE_DiplomatAI.description>A brain implant that contain AI. Able to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for diplomacy. Requires brain implants research before installing.</MSE_DiplomatAI.description>

  <MSE_TamerAI.label>tamer AI</MSE_TamerAI.label>
  <MSE_TamerAI.description>A brain implant that contain AI. Able to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for taming. Requires brain implants research before installing.</MSE_TamerAI.description>

  <MSE_ChefAI.label>chef AI</MSE_ChefAI.label>
  <MSE_ChefAI.description>A brain implant that contain AI. Able to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for cooking. Requires brain implants research before installing.</MSE_ChefAI.description>

  <MSE_HunterAI.label>hunter AI</MSE_HunterAI.label>
  <MSE_HunterAI.description>A brain implant that contain AI. Able to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for hunting. Requires brain implants research before installing.</MSE_HunterAI.description>

  <MSE_BasicLaborAI.label>basic labor AI</MSE_BasicLaborAI.label>
  <MSE_BasicLaborAI.description>A brain implant that contain AI. Able to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for basic unskilled labor. Requires brain implants research before installing.</MSE_BasicLaborAI.description>

  <MSE_AppetiteSuppressant.label>appetite suppressant</MSE_AppetiteSuppressant.label>
  <MSE_AppetiteSuppressant.description>A stomach implant that suppres hungry. Requires implants research before installing.</MSE_AppetiteSuppressant.description>


</LanguageData>