<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <MSE_AdvancedEndoskeletonStimulator.label>advanced endoskeleton stimulator</MSE_AdvancedEndoskeletonStimulator.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedEndoskeletonStimulator.description>An advanced torso implant that stimulates the overall muscles so they can operate at maximum performance. Requires archotech implants surgery research before installing.</MSE_AdvancedEndoskeletonStimulator.description>

  <MSE_AdvancedMuscleStimulator.label>advanced muscle stimulator</MSE_AdvancedMuscleStimulator.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedMuscleStimulator.description>An advanced muscle implant that stimulates the overall muscles so they can operate at maximum performance. Requires archotech implants surgery research before installing.</MSE_AdvancedMuscleStimulator.description>

  <AdvancedJoywire.label>advanced joywire</AdvancedJoywire.label>
  <AdvancedJoywire.description>An advanced brain implant that stimulates the brain's pleasure centers. It dramatically improves a user's mood without any side effect. Advanced Joywires are illegal on many worlds, and are known for destroying whole cultures. Requires archotech implants surgery research before installing.</AdvancedJoywire.description>

  <AdvancedPainstopper.label>advanced painstopper</AdvancedPainstopper.label>
  <AdvancedPainstopper.description>An advanced brain implant which inhibits nociception, or pain sensation. While it does allow the user to accomplish more, it turns out pain has a purpose. When you don't feel it, you can get hurt really bad really easily. Can be activated or deactivated according to user will. Requires archotech implants surgery research before installing.</AdvancedPainstopper.description>

  <MSE_AdvancedBuilderAI.label>advanced builder AI</MSE_AdvancedBuilderAI.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedBuilderAI.description>An advanced brain implant that contain AI. Capable to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for building. Requires archotech implants surgery research before installing.</MSE_AdvancedBuilderAI.description>

  <MSE_AdvancedFarmerAI.label>advanced farmer AI</MSE_AdvancedFarmerAI.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedFarmerAI.description>An advanced brain implant that contain AI. Capable to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for farming. Requires archotech implants surgery research before installing.</MSE_AdvancedFarmerAI.description>

  <MSE_AdvancedDoctorAI.label>advanced doctor AI</MSE_AdvancedDoctorAI.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedDoctorAI.description>An advanced brain implant that contain AI. Capable to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for doctoring. Requires archotech implants surgery research before installing.</MSE_AdvancedDoctorAI.description>

  <MSE_AdvancedMinerAI.label>advanced miner AI</MSE_AdvancedMinerAI.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedMinerAI.description>An advanced brain implant that contain AI. Capable to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for mining. Requires archotech implants surgery research before installing.</MSE_AdvancedMinerAI.description>

  <MSE_AdvancedDiplomatAI.label>advanced diplomat AI</MSE_AdvancedDiplomatAI.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedDiplomatAI.description>An advanced brain implant that contain AI. Able to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for diplomacy. Requires archotech implants surgery research before installing.</MSE_AdvancedDiplomatAI.description>

  <MSE_AdvancedTamerAI.label>advanced tamer AI</MSE_AdvancedTamerAI.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedTamerAI.description>An advanced brain implant that contain AI. Able to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for taming. Requires archotech implants surgery research before installing.</MSE_AdvancedTamerAI.description>

  <MSE_AdvancedChefAI.label>advanced chef AI</MSE_AdvancedChefAI.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedChefAI.description>An advanced brain implant that contain AI. Able to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for cooking. Requires archotech implants surgery research before installing.</MSE_AdvancedChefAI.description>

  <MSE_AdvancedHunterAI.label>advanced hunter AI</MSE_AdvancedHunterAI.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedHunterAI.description>An advanced brain implant that contain AI. Able to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for hunting. Requires archotech implants surgery research before installing.</MSE_AdvancedHunterAI.description>

  <MSE_AdvancedLaborAI.label>advanced labor AI</MSE_AdvancedLaborAI.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedLaborAI.description>An advanced brain implant that contain AI. Able to communicate with the user brain and act as a guide for advanced unskilled labor. Requires archotech implants surgery research before installing.</MSE_AdvancedLaborAI.description>

  <MSE_AdvancedAppetiteSuppressant.label>advanced appetite suppressant</MSE_AdvancedAppetiteSuppressant.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedAppetiteSuppressant.description>An advanced stomach implant that suppres hungry. Requires archotech implants surgery research before installing.</MSE_AdvancedAppetiteSuppressant.description>


</LanguageData>