<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <BionicLung.label>bionic lung</BionicLung.label>
  <BionicLung.description>An advanced artificial lung. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. It is better than a biological lung in almost every way. Requires bionic organs research to install it.</BionicLung.description>

  <BionicKidney.label>bionic kidney</BionicKidney.label>
  <BionicKidney.description>An advanced artificial kidney. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. It is better than a biological kidney in almost every way. Requires bionic organs research to install it.</BionicKidney.description>

  <BionicLiver.label>bionic liver</BionicLiver.label>
  <BionicLiver.description>An advanced artificial liver. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. It is better than a biological liver in almost every way. Requires bionic organs research to install it.</BionicLiver.description>

  <BionicFoot.label>bionic foot</BionicFoot.label>
  <BionicFoot.description>An advanced artificial foot. With its biogel nerve-link and lattice-dust healing system, it is better than a biological foot in almost every way. Requires bionics research to install it.</BionicFoot.description>

  <BionicToe.label>bionic toe</BionicToe.label>
  <BionicToe.description>An advanced artificial toe. With its biogel nerve-link and lattice-dust healing system, it is better than a biological toe in almost every way. Requires bionics research to install it.</BionicToe.description>

  <BionicShoulder.label>bionic shoulder</BionicShoulder.label>
  <BionicShoulder.description>An advanced artificial shoulder. With its biogel nerve-link and lattice-dust healing system, it is better than a biological shoulder in almost every way. Requires bionics research to install it.</BionicShoulder.description>

  <BionicHand.label>bionic hand</BionicHand.label>
  <BionicHand.description>An advanced artificial hand. With its biogel nerve-link and lattice-dust healing system, it is better than a biological hand in almost every way. Requires bionics research to install it.</BionicHand.description>

  <BionicFinger.label>bionic finger</BionicFinger.label>
  <BionicFinger.description>An advanced artificial finger. With its biogel nerve-link and lattice-dust healing system, it is better than a biological finger in almost every way. Requires bionics research to install it.</BionicFinger.description>

  <BionicJaw.label>bionic jaw</BionicJaw.label>
  <BionicJaw.description>An advanced artificial jaw. With its biogel nerve-link and lattice-dust healing system, it is better than a biological jaw in almost every way. Requires bionics research to install it.</BionicJaw.description>

  <BionicClavicle.label>bionic clavicle</BionicClavicle.label>
  <BionicClavicle.description>An advanced artificial clavicle. With lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. Requires bionic bones research to install it.</BionicClavicle.description>

  <BionicSternum.label>bionic sternum</BionicSternum.label>
  <BionicSternum.description>An advanced artificial sternum. With lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. Requires bionic bones research to install it.</BionicSternum.description>

  <BionicRib.label>bionic rib</BionicRib.label>
  <BionicRib.description>An advanced artificial rib. With lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. Requires bionic bones research to install it.</BionicRib.description>

  <BionicPelvis.label>bionic pelvis</BionicPelvis.label>
  <BionicPelvis.description>An advanced artificial pelvis. With lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. Requires bionic bones research to install it.</BionicPelvis.description>

  <BionicHumerus.label>bionic humerus</BionicHumerus.label>
  <BionicHumerus.description>An advanced artificial humerus. With lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. Requires bionic bones research to install it.</BionicHumerus.description>

  <BionicRadius.label>bionic radius</BionicRadius.label>
  <BionicRadius.description>An advanced artificial radius. With lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. Requires bionic bones research to install it.</BionicRadius.description>

  <BionicFemur.label>bionic femur</BionicFemur.label>
  <BionicFemur.description>An advanced artificial femur. With lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. Requires bionic bones research to install it.</BionicFemur.description>

  <BionicTibia.label>bionic tibia</BionicTibia.label>
  <BionicTibia.description>An advanced artificial tibia. With lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. Requires bionic bones research to install it.</BionicTibia.description>


</LanguageData>