<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <MSE_ArchotechClavicleModule.label>archotech clavicle module</MSE_ArchotechClavicleModule.label>
  <MSE_ArchotechClavicleModule.description>An artifical clavicle module built by an archotech. It's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. You can install it to clavicle module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_ArchotechClavicleModule.description>

  <MSE_ArchotechArmModule.label>archotech arm module</MSE_ArchotechArmModule.label>
  <MSE_ArchotechArmModule.description>An artifical arm module built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural arm, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. You can install it to arm module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_ArchotechArmModule.description>

  <MSE_ArchotechHumerusModule.label>archotech humerus module</MSE_ArchotechHumerusModule.label>
  <MSE_ArchotechHumerusModule.description>An artifical humerus module built by an archotech. It's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. You can install it to humerus module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_ArchotechHumerusModule.description>

  <MSE_ArchotechRadiusModule.label>archotech radius module</MSE_ArchotechRadiusModule.label>
  <MSE_ArchotechRadiusModule.description>An artifical radius module built by an archotech. It's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. You can install it to radius module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_ArchotechRadiusModule.description>

  <MSE_ArchotechHandModule.label>archotech hand module</MSE_ArchotechHandModule.label>
  <MSE_ArchotechHandModule.description>An artifical hand module built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural hand, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. You can install it to hand module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_ArchotechHandModule.description>

  <MSE_ArchotechFingerModule.label>archotech finger module</MSE_ArchotechFingerModule.label>
  <MSE_ArchotechFingerModule.description>An artifical finger module built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural finger, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. You can install it to finger module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_ArchotechFingerModule.description>

  <MSE_ArchotechFemurModule.label>archotech femur module</MSE_ArchotechFemurModule.label>
  <MSE_ArchotechFemurModule.description>An artifical femur module built by an archotech. It's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. You can install it to femur module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_ArchotechFemurModule.description>

  <MSE_ArchotechTibiaModule.label>archotech tibia module</MSE_ArchotechTibiaModule.label>
  <MSE_ArchotechTibiaModule.description>An artifical tibia module built by an archotech. It's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. You can install it to tibia module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_ArchotechTibiaModule.description>

  <MSE_ArchotechFootModule.label>archotech foot module</MSE_ArchotechFootModule.label>
  <MSE_ArchotechFootModule.description>An artifical foot module built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural foot, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. You can install it to foot module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_ArchotechFootModule.description>

  <MSE_ArchotechToeModule.label>archotech toe module</MSE_ArchotechToeModule.label>
  <MSE_ArchotechToeModule.description>An artifical toe module built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural toe, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. You can install it to toe module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_ArchotechToeModule.description>


</LanguageData>