<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!--[Core] <Heart.label>сердце</Heart.label>-->
  <!--[Core] <Heart.description>Человеческое сердце. Доставляет кровь и кислород ко всем частям тела. Готово найти нового владельца.</Heart.description>-->

  <!--[Core] <Lung.label>лёгкое</Lung.label>-->
  <!--[Core] <Lung.description>Человеческое лёгкое. Незаменимая часть дыхательной системы.</Lung.description>-->

  <!--[Core] <Kidney.label>почка</Kidney.label>-->
  <!--[Core] <Kidney.description>Человеческая почка. Отфильтровывает и удаляет отходы метаболизма из крови.</Kidney.description>-->

  <!--[Core] <Liver.label>печень</Liver.label>-->
  <!--[Core] <Liver.description>Человеческая печень. Играет важную роль в обмене веществ.</Liver.description>-->

  <Brain.label>brain cells</Brain.label>
  <Brain.description>A biological brain cells. The main core of almost all organic life. Requires organ transplantation research to transplant it.</Brain.description>

  <Stomach.label>stomach</Stomach.label>
  <Stomach.description>A biological stomach. Digests food and turns it into energy. Requires organ transplantation research to transplant it.</Stomach.description>

  <Leg.label>leg</Leg.label>
  <Leg.description>A biological leg. Lets you move around. Requires organ transplantation research to transplant it.</Leg.description>

  <Foot.label>foot</Foot.label>
  <Foot.description>A biological foot. Part of leg that lets you move around. Requires organ transplantation research to transplant it.</Foot.description>

  <Toe.label>toe</Toe.label>
  <Toe.description>A biological toe. Part of foot that helps you move around. Requires organ transplantation research to transplant it.</Toe.description>

  <Shoulder.label>shoulder</Shoulder.label>
  <Shoulder.description>A biological shoulder. Lets you work and carry stuff. Requires organ transplantation research to transplant it.</Shoulder.description>

  <Arm.label>arm</Arm.label>
  <Arm.description>A biological arm. Lets you work and carry stuff. Requires organ transplantation research to transplant it.</Arm.description>

  <Hand.label>hand</Hand.label>
  <Hand.description>A biological hand. Part of arm that lets you work and carry stuff. Requires organ transplantation research to transplant it.</Hand.description>

  <Finger.label>finger</Finger.label>
  <Finger.description>A biological finger. Part of hand that helps you work and carry stuff. Requires organ transplantation research to transplant it.</Finger.description>

  <Eye.label>eye</Eye.label>
  <Eye.description>A biological eye. Absorbs light, which lets a person to see. Requires organ transplantation research to transplant it.</Eye.description>

  <Ear.label>ear</Ear.label>
  <Ear.description>A biological ear. Picks up vibrations, allowing people to hear sound. Requires organ transplantation research to transplant it.</Ear.description>

  <Nose.label>nose</Nose.label>
  <Nose.description>A biological nose. The finishing touch to a face. Requires organ transplantation research to transplant it.</Nose.description>

  <Jaw.label>jaw</Jaw.label>
  <Jaw.description>A biological jaw. Allow people to eat and socializing. Requires organ transplantation research to transplant it.</Jaw.description>


</LanguageData>