<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <MSE_AdvancedRangedPlatformModule.label>advanced ranged platform module</MSE_AdvancedRangedPlatformModule.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedRangedPlatformModule.description>An advanced ranged platform module. If it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. With stabilizer and targeting system can give your pawn great accuracy and turn your pawn to specialized for ranged combat. You can install it to clavicle module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_AdvancedRangedPlatformModule.description>

  <MSE_AdvancedMeleePlatformModule.label>advanced melee platform module</MSE_AdvancedMeleePlatformModule.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedMeleePlatformModule.description>An advanced melee platform module. If it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. With sensory motor and targeting system can give your pawn great melee damage and turn your pawn to specialized for melee combat. You can install it to clavicle module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_AdvancedMeleePlatformModule.description>

  <MSE_AdvancedPowerArmModule.label>advanced power arm module</MSE_AdvancedPowerArmModule.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedPowerArmModule.description>An advanced power arm module built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural arm, have high blunt damage, and it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. You can install it to arm module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_AdvancedPowerArmModule.description>

  <MSE_AdvancedPowerClawModule.label>advanced power claw module</MSE_AdvancedPowerClawModule.label>
  <MSE_AdvancedPowerClawModule.description>An advanced power claw module built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural hand, has sharp claw attached to it, and it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. You can install it to hand module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_AdvancedPowerClawModule.description>

  <MSE_AdamantiumBoneModule.label>adamantium bone module</MSE_AdamantiumBoneModule.label>
  <MSE_AdamantiumBoneModule.description>A bone module that crafted with high quality adamantium alloy. Able to sustain almost all attack. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. You can install it to all bone module slot. Requires modules surgery research to install it.</MSE_AdamantiumBoneModule.description>


</LanguageData>