<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Human Hybrid Implants -->

  <GR_BearClaws.label>человеческий имплант: bear claws</GR_BearClaws.label>
  <GR_BearClaws.description>An improvement over the bionic Power Claw, these claws have been vat-grown with a mixture of human and bear DNA, and replace the subject's hand with versatile, non-retractable claws.</GR_BearClaws.description>

  <GR_DiggingBearClaws.label>человеческий имплант: digging bear claws</GR_DiggingBearClaws.label>
  <GR_DiggingBearClaws.description>Grotesque but powerful hand blades that have been modified to be used in mining operations, increasing both speed and yield.</GR_DiggingBearClaws.description>

  <GR_BearMuscleTissue.label>человеческий имплант: bear muscle tissue</GR_BearMuscleTissue.label>
  <GR_BearMuscleTissue.description>Grafts of bear muscle tissue on the subject's torso increase overall strength and stamina. These grafts however tend to stimulate the production of an abundance of body hair.</GR_BearMuscleTissue.description>

  <GR_HibernationModule.label>человеческий имплант: hibernation module</GR_HibernationModule.label>
  <GR_HibernationModule.description>A biochip that modifies the brain to reduce the need for sleep.</GR_HibernationModule.description>

  <GR_Ovipositor.label>человеческий имплант: ovipositor</GR_Ovipositor.label>
  <GR_Ovipositor.description>You know you have gone too far in your scientific experiments when you are implanting a human being with an ovipositor. This will enable the colonist to lay chicken eggs twice a day. It hurts as hell, though. Also, yuck.</GR_Ovipositor.description>

  <GR_MuffaloMuscles.label>человеческий имплант: muffalo strengthened muscles</GR_MuffaloMuscles.label>
  <GR_MuffaloMuscles.description>By weaving muffalo muscle strands with the subjects muscular system, strength, resilience and carrying capacity are greatly increased.</GR_MuffaloMuscles.description>

  <GR_MuffaloMammaries.label>человеческий имплант: muffalo mammaries</GR_MuffaloMammaries.label>
  <GR_MuffaloMammaries.description>By implanting muffalo mammaries into a colonist... Wait, what??? Who came up with this idea????? Anyway... this implant allows your colonist to be milked... Ugh, I give up.</GR_MuffaloMammaries.description>

  <GR_MuffaloSkin.label>человеческий имплант: muffalo skin</GR_MuffaloSkin.label>
  <GR_MuffaloSkin.description>A synthetic skin substitute that is much thicker and a much better insulator than human skin. This provides a measure of defense but, more importantly, makes the subject more resistant to low temperatures.</GR_MuffaloSkin.description>

  <GR_BoomalopeNodules.label>человеческий имплант: boomalope nodules</GR_BoomalopeNodules.label>
  <GR_BoomalopeNodules.description>These skin nodules can be integrated in a human's torso, causing a huge explosion if the subjects dies violently.</GR_BoomalopeNodules.description>

  <GR_ChemfuelStomach.label>человеческий имплант: chemfuel stomach</GR_ChemfuelStomach.label>
  <GR_ChemfuelStomach.description>A reinforced bionic stomach that uses a combination of gastric acid and chemfuel to efficiently digest food.</GR_ChemfuelStomach.description>

  <GR_ChemfuelHeart.label>человеческий имплант: chemfuel heart</GR_ChemfuelHeart.label>
  <GR_ChemfuelHeart.description>A reinforced bionic heart that acts like a miniature 4-stroke internal combustion engine powered by chemfuel to pump blood through the body.</GR_ChemfuelHeart.description>

  <GR_WolfMuscularFibers.label>человеческий имплант: wolf muscular fibers</GR_WolfMuscularFibers.label>
  <GR_WolfMuscularFibers.description>The subjects legs can be modified by weaving hybrid human/wolf muscle fibers within the base tissue, giving her a significant strength and speed boost.</GR_WolfMuscularFibers.description>

  <GR_DevouringJaws.label>человеческий имплант: devouring jaws</GR_DevouringJaws.label>
  <GR_DevouringJaws.description>A set of improved teeth designed to rapidly chew and ingest any kind of food. Leaves kind of a mess, though...</GR_DevouringJaws.description>

  <GR_NeuronReinforcement.label>человеческий имплант: neuron reinforcement</GR_NeuronReinforcement.label>
  <GR_NeuronReinforcement.description>A biochip using animal stem cells to reinforce the natural abilities of human neurons, increasing learning and research speed.</GR_NeuronReinforcement.description>

  <GR_MousePheromones.label>человеческий имплант: mouse pheromones</GR_MousePheromones.label>
  <GR_MousePheromones.description>A bionic vomeronasal organ that allows the subject pheromonal communication with other animals, increasing the chance of taming and training them successfully.</GR_MousePheromones.description>

  <GR_MoleratNerveDampener.label>человеческий имплант: mole-rat nerve dampener</GR_MoleratNerveDampener.label>
  <GR_MoleratNerveDampener.description>A biochip that reduces pain sensitivity, allowing the subject to survive pain shock.</GR_MoleratNerveDampener.description>

  <GR_BunnyEars.label>человеческий имплант: bunny ear</GR_BunnyEars.label>
  <GR_BunnyEars.description>This huge leporid ear gives amazing enhanced hearing. Also, super kawaii!</GR_BunnyEars.description>

  <GR_InsectoidAntennae.label>человеческий имплант: insectoid antennae</GR_InsectoidAntennae.label>
  <GR_InsectoidAntennae.description>These hybrid humanoid / insectoid feeling appendages can be implanted in a subject's head, completely modifying the way the subject "sees" and feels the surrounding world. The experience may be slightly overwhelming due to sensorial overload.</GR_InsectoidAntennae.description>

  <GR_PsychicDampeners.label>человеческий имплант: psychic dampeners</GR_PsychicDampeners.label>
  <GR_PsychicDampeners.description>Artificial hearing aids that block psychic emanations, providing considerable resistance to mechanoids' psychic attacks.</GR_PsychicDampeners.description>

  <GR_KidneyToxicFilters.label>человеческий имплант: kidney toxic filters</GR_KidneyToxicFilters.label>
  <GR_KidneyToxicFilters.description>This is a bioelectronic kidney prosthesis that greatly improves the efficiency of the subject's kidney by using insectoid tissue, providing resistence to toxic substances.</GR_KidneyToxicFilters.description>

  <GR_HumanThrumboHorn.label>человеческий имплант: thrumbo horn</GR_HumanThrumboHorn.label>
  <GR_HumanThrumboHorn.description>A genetically modified thrumbo horn that can be implanted in a subject's forehead. Nasty.</GR_HumanThrumboHorn.description>

  <GR_ThrumboSkin.label>человеческий имплант: thrumbo skin</GR_ThrumboSkin.label>
  <GR_ThrumboSkin.description>A synthetic skin substitute that is much thicker and a much better insulator than human skin. This provides a lot of defense and makes the subject more resistant to extremes of temperature.</GR_ThrumboSkin.description>

  <GR_VenomousFangs.label>человеческий имплант: venomous fangs</GR_VenomousFangs.label>
  <GR_VenomousFangs.description>This hybrid implant substitutes the subject's jaw with a set of venomous fangs. Useful in combat, but not very comfortable.</GR_VenomousFangs.description>

  <GR_IguanaScales.label>человеческий имплант: iguana scales</GR_IguanaScales.label>
  <GR_IguanaScales.description>A synthetic skin substitute that is much thicker and a much better insulator than human skin. This provides a measure of defense but, more importantly, makes the subject more resistant to high temperatures.</GR_IguanaScales.description>


</LanguageData>