<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Cat - Bear -->

  <GR_Catbear.label>catbear</GR_Catbear.label>
  <GR_Catbear.description>A cat / bear hybrid. Catbears are intelligent and affectionate, a perfect companion. They are also quite more resilient than your average cat.\n\nUseful abilities: Like all cat hybrids, they have an improved melee dodge ability, which in the case of these small animals is ideal to get out of a fight, and a short nuzzle period.</GR_Catbear.description>
  <GR_Catbear.tools.0.label>left claw</GR_Catbear.tools.0.label>
  <GR_Catbear.tools.1.label>right claw</GR_Catbear.tools.1.label>
  <GR_Catbear.tools.3.label>head</GR_Catbear.tools.3.label>
  <!-- Use Leather From: Cat -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Cat -->
  <GR_Catbear_Corpse.label>catbear corpse</GR_Catbear_Corpse.label>
  <GR_Catbear_Corpse.description>catbear corpse</GR_Catbear_Corpse.description>


  <!-- Cat - Boomalope -->

  <GR_Catalope.label>catalope</GR_Catalope.label>
  <GR_Catalope.description>A cat / boomalope hybrid. It's like a miniature boomalope! Or a exploding kitten! Terrifying either way.\n\nUseful abilities: Like all cat hybrids, they have an improved melee dodge ability, which in the case of these small animals is ideal to get out of a fight, and a short nuzzle period. The catalope produces small quantities of chemfuel, and explodes with a tiny hairball cloud.</GR_Catalope.description>
  <GR_Catalope.tools.1.label>head</GR_Catalope.tools.1.label>
  <!-- Use Leather From: Cat -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Boomalope -->
  <GR_Catalope_Corpse.label>catalope corpse</GR_Catalope_Corpse.label>
  <GR_Catalope_Corpse.description>catalope corpse</GR_Catalope_Corpse.description>


  <!-- Cat - Chicken -->

  <GR_Catchicken.label>catchicken</GR_Catchicken.label>
  <GR_Catchicken.description>A cat / chicken hybrid. Catchicken might not be as intelligent as other cat hybrids, but they make up for it with their ability to lay eggs quickly.\n\nUseful abilities: Like all cat hybrids, they have an improved melee dodge ability, which in the case of these small animals is ideal to get out of a fight, and a short nuzzle period. Quite fast egg laying.</GR_Catchicken.description>
  <GR_Catchicken.tools.1.label>head</GR_Catchicken.tools.1.label>
  <!-- Use Leather From: Cat -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Chicken -->
  <GR_Catchicken_Corpse.label>catchicken corpse</GR_Catchicken_Corpse.label>
  <GR_Catchicken_Corpse.description>catchicken corpse</GR_Catchicken_Corpse.description>


  <!-- Cat - Muffalo -->

  <GR_Catfallo.label>catfallo</GR_Catfallo.label>
  <GR_Catfallo.description>A cat / muffalo hybrid. The catfallo is slightly larger than other cat hybrids, and can be used as a miniature pack beast.\n\nUseful abilities: Like all cat hybrids, they have an improved melee dodge ability, which in the case of these small animals is ideal to get out of a fight, and a short nuzzle period. It produces milk and wool in small amounts.</GR_Catfallo.description>
  <GR_Catfallo.tools.0.label>head</GR_Catfallo.tools.0.label>
  <GR_Catfallo.tools.1.label>left hoof</GR_Catfallo.tools.1.label>
  <GR_Catfallo.tools.2.label>right hoof</GR_Catfallo.tools.2.label>
  <!-- Use Leather From: Cat -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Cat -->
  <GR_Catfallo_Corpse.label>catfallo corpse</GR_Catfallo_Corpse.label>
  <GR_Catfallo_Corpse.description>catfallo corpse</GR_Catfallo_Corpse.description>


  <!-- Cat - Rabbit -->

  <GR_Catrabbit.label>catrabbit</GR_Catrabbit.label>
  <GR_Catrabbit.description>A cat / rabbit hybrid. This long-eared cat breeds extremely fast, and is intelligent enough to be trained in the most basic sense.\n\nUseful abilities: Like all cat hybrids, they have an improved melee dodge ability, which in the case of these small animals is ideal to get out of a fight, and a short nuzzle period. Very fast breeding.</GR_Catrabbit.description>
  <GR_Catrabbit.tools.0.label>left claw</GR_Catrabbit.tools.0.label>
  <GR_Catrabbit.tools.1.label>right claw</GR_Catrabbit.tools.1.label>
  <GR_Catrabbit.tools.3.label>head</GR_Catrabbit.tools.3.label>
  <!-- Use Leather From: Cat -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Cat -->
  <GR_Catrabbit_Corpse.label>catrabbit corpse</GR_Catrabbit_Corpse.label>
  <GR_Catrabbit_Corpse.description>catrabbit corpse</GR_Catrabbit_Corpse.description>


  <!-- Cat - Wolf -->

  <GR_Catwolf.label>catwolf</GR_Catwolf.label>
  <GR_Catwolf.description>A cat / wolf hybrid. Catwolves are extremely intelligent cat hybrids, and they can be trained to haul. Not much, mind you, since they are quite small, but if you have an army of them the net result will be the same. Another positive note is that you will have hauling cats without needing to delve into the depths of weird weeaboo catgirl mods. NO SIR, we have enough weirdness here with the ovipositors and such.\n\nUseful abilities: Like all cat hybrids, they have an improved melee dodge ability, which in the case of these small animals is ideal to get out of a fight, and a short nuzzle period. Fast and intelligent.</GR_Catwolf.description>
  <GR_Catwolf.tools.0.label>left claw</GR_Catwolf.tools.0.label>
  <GR_Catwolf.tools.1.label>right claw</GR_Catwolf.tools.1.label>
  <GR_Catwolf.tools.3.label>head</GR_Catwolf.tools.3.label>
  <!-- Use Leather From: Cat -->
  <!-- Use Meat From: Cat -->
  <GR_Catwolf_Corpse.label>catwolf corpse</GR_Catwolf_Corpse.label>
  <GR_Catwolf_Corpse.description>catwolf corpse</GR_Catwolf_Corpse.description>


</LanguageData>